Getting a good grade from a subject,
いい成績を修めること
is seen by most students and parents as the most easy
それは、多くの生徒や保護者から学校での結果の最も簡単で わかりやすい
and simple measure of results in school.
指標として認識されています
Now, how are classes graded at Bodwell?
では、 Bodwellではどのように成績をつけられているのでしょうか？
Grades are in the form of an average percentage
成績はパーセンテージと
ora letter grade.
レターグレードでだされます
For example, a student getting 95 in Physics 11 is an A
例えば、物理学11で95%をおさめた場合、この生徒のレターグレードはAとなります
That shows a very high overall achievement by the student in Physics 11.
これは、物理学11の学生による非常に高い全体的な成果を示しています
Then there are B, C, and Fail.
それからB、C、そして落第点（F）があります
What is the fuller meaning involved in the grade?
成績が持つ深い意味とはなんだと思いますか？
In fact, how much a student understands, thinks, and uses knowledge in any subject
実際に、学生がどの科目でどの程度理解し、思考し、学んだ内容を応用するかは、
is not told by just one letter grade of A or B or C.
A、BまたはCの1文字のグレードだけでは分かりません
A master teacher uses many ways
教師達は、学生の学習、思考、理解について、
to observe, measure, and provide feedback
さまざまな方法で観察、測定し、
on a student's learning, thinking, and understanding.
フィードバックを提供しています
Mostly, a student learns and presents his learning by answering questions,
ほとんどの場合、学生はクイズやテスト、試験の形式、
oral or written,
口頭または書面による質問に答えることによって、
in the form of quizzes, tests, and exams.
学習し、学習成果を提示します
When these are the same across classes or schools.
クイズ、テスト、試験形式がクラス、または学校を通して統一されている場合、
We use the term "Standardized Assessment".
我々は、"Standardized Assessment (標準化された評価方式)”という用語を使用します
A student also learns by discussing, arguing,
また、生徒は、議論・討論すること、
solving problems, designing and completing a project,
問題を解決すること、プロジェクトを設計して完了すること、
and working with other students.
他の生徒と一緒に働くことによっても学びます
Good teachers observe all these actions
良い教師はこれらすべての行動を観察し、
and give students feedback to provoke further thinking and questioning.
学生にさらなる考え、見解や疑問を引き起こすようなフィードバックを与えます
The teacher is measuring the student's learning
教師は、"Formative Process(形成プロセス)”を通して
Through a "Formative Process".
学生の学習経過やその結果を測定しています
All performances combined into one, final grade.
すべての経過・結果は1つにまとめられ、それが最終グレードとなります
A final grade for a subject will mean
各科目の最終成績は、
combining all that a students learns from
学生がクイズ、テスト、試験、ディスカッション、
quizzes, tests, and exams
宿題、グループプロジェクト、プレゼンテーションから学んだ、
discussions, homework, group projects, and presentations.
すべてのものを組み合わせることを意味します
What is a G.P.A.? - Grade Point Average
G.P.Aとは何でしょう？ - 成績総合平均点です
Transcripts give a G.P.A.
成績表にはG.P.A.が表示されます
meaning that the letter grades are changed into points.
レターグレードは点数に変換され、計算されます
A is 4, B-3, C-2. D or "PASS" - 1, Fail is a 0.
A は4点, Bは3点, Cは2点. D or "PASS" は-1点, Fail (落第)は 0点です
The in-betweens of A and B and C and D are a half point.
AとBとCとDの 中間点は半分の点（.5点）です
All points of various subjects are added
G.P.A.は、すべての科目のポイントを足し、
then divided by the number of subjects.
科目数で割った平均点です
If you still have questions about grades and G.P.A.,
もし成績とG.P.Aについて質問がある場合は、
Please speak to any teacher or counsellor.
教師やカウンセラーに相談してください